<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<site>
   <feature url="features/de.babe.eclipse.features.MC_2.1.1.jar" id="de.babe.eclipse.features.MC" version="2.1.1">
      <category name="Multi Clipboard"/>
   </feature>
   <feature url="features/de.babe.eclipse.features.tinyHTML_1.1.1.jar" id="de.babe.eclipse.features.tinyHTML" version="1.1.1">
      <category name="tiny HTML Tools"/>
   </feature>
   <feature url="features/de.babe.eclipse.features.QuickREx_3.5.0.jar" id="de.babe.eclipse.features.QuickREx" version="3.5.0">
      <category name="QuickREx"/>
   </feature>
   <feature url="features/de.babe.eclipse.features.QuickREx_I18N_1.0.0.jar" id="de.babe.eclipse.features.QuickREx_I18N" version="1.0.0">
      <category name="QuickREx"/>
   </feature>
   <feature url="features/de.babe.eclipse.features.XPathDeveloper_1.0.1.jar" id="de.babe.eclipse.features.XPathDeveloper" version="1.0.1">
      <category name="XPath-Developer"/>
   </feature>
   <feature url="features/de.babe.eclipse.features.Tools_2.0.0.jar" id="de.babe.eclipse.features.Tools" version="2.0.0">
      <category name="Tools"/>
   </feature>
   <category-def name="Tools" label="Tools">
      <description>
         Useful Tools for Eclipse - Bundles &apos;Multi Clipboard&apos;, &apos;QuickREx&apos; and &apos;tiny HTML Tools&apos;
In case you do not want all plugins contained in this feature to be installed, select the ones you want 
separately in the update manager.
      </description>
   </category-def>
   <category-def name="Multi Clipboard" label="Multi Clipboard">
      <description>
         Multi Clipboard gives you a clipboard for text- and source-code
editor contents that holds multiple entries. You can collect
some snippets by adding them to the Multi Clipboard and then
paste any of them to where you need them.
You can configure the plug-in to save the contents of your Multi
Clipboard to a file when Eclipse is closed. Contents are then
reloaded when Eclipse is opened. You can even configure the plug-in
to enable editing the contents of the Multi Clipboard.
      </description>
   </category-def>
   <category-def name="tiny HTML Tools" label="tiny HTML Tools">
      <description>
         tiny HTML Tools are just what the name suggests: A set of very
small but useful actions added to the Eclipse text-editor which
let you write simple formatted HTML-contents easier.
      </description>
   </category-def>
   <category-def name="QuickREx" label="QuickREx">
      <description>
         QuickREx is a tool to test, play with, and use Regular Expressions.
It offers evaluation as-you-type and highlighting of matches,
navigation through matches and navigation through groups 
in matches as well as grepping (extracting) matches.
You can save regular expressions and test-texts that they are
matched against into a persistent store for later reference.
You can also load file-contents as test-texts.
      </description>
   </category-def>
   <category-def name="XPath-Developer" label="XPath-Developer">
      <description>
         XPath-Developer is a tool to test, play with, and use XPath Expressions.
It offers evaluation as-you-type or on-demand and allows to choose
the output-type. It also offers TAB-Completion.
You can save expressions into a persistent store for later reference.
      </description>
   </category-def>
</site>
